Trust me.
Liar Liar is a comedy film directed by Tom Shadyac.
Forced by his son's birthday wish, fast-talking attorney and habitual liar
Fletcher Reede must tell the truth for the next 24 hours.
Fletcher Reede, played by Jim Carrey.
Audrey Reede, played by Maura Tierney.
Max Reede, played by Justin Cooper.
Jerry, played by Cary Elwes.
Greta, played by Anne Haney.
Miranda, played by Amanda Donohoe.
Liar Liar is a 1997 American fantasy comedy film starring Jim Carrey as a lawyer who built his entire
career on lying only to find himself cursed to speak only the truth for a single day.
He struggles to maintain his career and to reconcile with his ex-wife
and son whom he alienated with his pathological lying.
The film was directed by Tom Shadyac, and is the second of three collaborations
between Carrey and Shadyac, the first being Ace Ventura: Pet Detective.
Liar Liar was released in the United States on
March 18, 1997 by Universal Pictures.
The film received positive reviews from critics, and grossed
$303 million against a budget of $45 million.
At the 55th Golden Globe Awards, Carrey was nominated for Best Actor.
The film explores themes of california, workaholic, truth, honesty, liar.
The tone is lighthearted.